《嘻哈帝国》前情提要
Previously on Empire...
看起来邦基和肖恩・约翰逊的关系相当好啊
Looks like Bunkie been real tight with Shyne Johnson.
他们四个就是你那时候杀掉的毒贩
Them four dealers you killed back in the day?
你是个杀人凶手
You is a murderer.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
我愿意
Yes.
你觉得有人推了你一把
You think that someone pushed you?
我不知道
I don't know.
听着 我知道你是联邦调查局的人 塔里克 所以你最好别动小心思
Look, I know you a Fed, Tariq, so you better not be planning on
逼我妹妹
putting the squeeze on my sister
来找我或者我家人的麻烦
to try to come for me or my family.
-枪 -不 不 不 停下 弗雷达 不要
- Gun! - No, no, no! Stop, Freda! No!
贾马尔
Jamal!
里昂先生和里昂太太
Mr. And Mrs. Lyon?
# You say you're right #
# I'll say you're wrong #
# You'll be polite... #
嘿
Hey!
# But continue on... #
你看起来
You look like
减了不少重啊 伙计
you lost some weight, man.
感觉怎样 伙计 你还好吧 兄弟
How you doing, man? You good, brother?
我很想你 伙计
Miss you, man.
你能回来我们真的很高兴 已经过了这么久了
We're so glad you're back! It's been so long.
# Ooh... #
# You say it's night #
# And I'll say it's morning #
# You'll see the light #
# And pretend you don't #
# And I'll close the blinds #
# If you really want me to #
# If that's what you want to do #
# But life has its own #
# Arranges #
# As time passes on #
# And changes #
# The hourglass moves on a grain #
# And our path is torn and strained. #
真能唱啊 姑娘
You better sing, girl!
是啊 维 是啊
Yeah, V. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
谢谢夸奖
Something like that.
你觉得怎样 很棒 对吧
What do you think? It's hot, right?
我觉得这首歌很适合你弟弟的婚礼
Think it'll be great for your brother's wedding.
是的 我希望你能和维一起唱这首歌
Yeah, I want you and V to sing it together.
棒呆了 对吧
It's dope, right?
实在太美了 维罗妮卡
It's beautiful, Veronica.
谢谢 贾马尔
Thanks, Jamal.
早跟你说了的
Told you.
不过你们得另外再找人来合唱了
Y'all got to find somebody else to sing it with you though,
因为我不会表演的
'cause I'm not gonna perform.
不 不 你要表演 贾马尔
No. Yes, you are, Jamal.
你这样讲只是因为你现在太累了
You just saying that 'cause you're tired right now.
听着 你父亲为了你把他的健身房改成了复健室
Look, your father turned his gym into a rehab just for you.
不 我真正做的是
No, what I actually did,
给你找到了最好的理疗师
I got the top physical therapist,
就是那个把佩顿・曼宁从他脖颈旧伤中
the same dude that put Peyton Manning together
拯救出来的家伙
after that big old neck injury of his.
他说过他能让你
He said he's gonna have you
在几周内重回巅峰 儿子
in tip-top shape in a couple weeks, son.
看吧
See?
听着 我们 我们希望你能够在我们的婚礼上唱歌
Look, we... we want you to sing at our wedding.
是的 我们非常希望
Yes, we would love that.
德雷甚至受戒了 这样他就能主持婚礼仪式
Look, Dre even got ordained so he can do the ceremony.
他来主持我们的婚礼 马尔
He gonna marry us, Mal.
所以我希望我的两个兄弟都在场
So I want both of my brothers to be there.
就是这样
Period.
也许我们应该让他一个人静一会儿 让他休息休息
Maybe we should leave him alone, let him get some rest.
如果你感觉不好的话 我们甚至能推迟婚礼
Look, we can even postpone it if you're not feeling...
我不会再唱歌了 好吗
I ain't singing no more, all right?
很抱歉 各位 我只是 我只是太累了
I'm sorry, man. I'm just... I'm just tired.
你们没有感觉到疲惫吗
Ain't y'all tired?
一直是相同的循环
The same damn cycle all the time.
总是死亡和监禁循环往复
Just death and incarceration.
我们本能够改变这个循环
We could change that cycle.
在我们做到这点之前 我不会再唱歌
I ain't singing again until we do.
不要这样 孩子 你在说些什么啊
Come on, man. What are you talking about?
你难道没意识到如果不是你的话
Don't you realize if it hadn't been for you,
我都活不到现在 孩子
I might not even be here, man.
你不用因为这个而感谢我 爸
You ain't got to thank me for that, Dad.
不 不 我的意思是 你替我挡了一枪 宝贝
No, no. I mean... I mean, you took a bullet for me, baby.
这是我永远不会忘记的
That's something I will never forget.
那弗雷达呢
How's Freda?
你是说那个想要杀了我的姑娘
You mean the girl that tried to shoot me?
她也是其中的受害者 她也是 她也是受害者
She's a victim in this. She is. She's a victim, too.
就像他 我 还有他一样
Just like him and me and him.
-贾马尔 -德怀特
- Jamal. - Dwight,
你和这些孩子们
you and them kids
都是偿还你父亲欠下的血债
is paying for the crimes of your daddy.
德怀特 德怀特 藏在这儿 这儿
Dwight, Dwight, hide over here. Here.
嘘
Shh.
-你在说什么呀 奶奶 -好了
- What are you talking about, Grandma? - Okay.
贾马尔脾气不好是因为他累了
Jamal is grumpy because he's tired.
他以前可没被枪射中过
He ain't never been shot before.
所以我要把他带回他房间了
So I'm gonna take him to his room.
你之前说过我们的爷爷是个警察
You said our grandfather was a cop.
我爸确实是个警察
My daddy was a cop.
好了
Okay.
到你睡午觉的时间了
It's time for you to take your nap.
胡安妮塔会给你一小杯可口的白兰地
Juanita's gonna bring you up a nice little brandy.
来
Come on.
跟大家说再见
Say good-bye to everybody.
大家再见
Good-bye to everybody.
幸好当时瑟斯赶在你对那些记者
You're lucky Thirsty caught you
胡言乱语之前就找到了你 算你走运
before you blabbed to all those reporters.
你要是再继续捏我的胳膊
You keep squeezing my arm,
我就用脚狠狠踢你的嘴
and I'm gonna check your damn mouth with my foot.
听着 这是我的房子
Look, this is my house.
只有我才能对我的孩子们讲我的过去
I'm the only one that talks to my children about my past.
你听明白了吗
Is that clear?
告诉他们真相
Tell them the truth.
胡安妮塔
Juanita!
我很担心他
I'm worried about him.
我是说 不是因为
I mean, and it's not because
他不愿做理疗
he doesn't want to do physical therapy.
-而是他看起来很消颓 卢修斯 -是啊
- He seems off, Lucious. - Yeah.
医生说他可以行走了 但是
Doctors said he should be walking, but, um...
他不想再做音乐
he don't want to do music.
是啊 这就是我最担心的
Yeah, that's what concerns me.
请进
Come in.
卡尔汗女士找你
I got Ms. Calhoun for you.
嘿
Hey.
我孙子还好吧
How's my grandbaby?
老实说 他现在有点紧张
He's a little stressed out right now, to be honest.
你现在有时间让我和你单独谈谈吗
Do you have a moment where I can speak with you privately?
琦琦和我之间没有秘密
Cookie and me ain't got no secrets.
姑娘 坐下
Girl, sit down.
前几天 几个联邦调查局探员
I was picked up by a couple of federal agents
找上了我
the other day.
是塔里克 我早跟你说了
Tariq. I told your ass.
在他们表达了想要我配合他们的愿望之后
After they told me what they might have wanted from me,
我强烈要求离开
I absolutely demanded to be allowed to leave.
是的 但是现在 显然
Yeah, but now, of course,
他们想要传唤她出庭 不能让这事发生啊
they're gonna try to subpoena her. Can't let that happen.
我们会给你安排全天候的安保
We're gonna get 24-hour security around you.
好了 他们说了什么
Okay, what did they say?
他们问了你什么样的问题
What kind of questions did they ask you?
他们问了很多问题
They were asking a lot.
我一个也没回答
I didn't answer any of them.
姑娘 你总该记得点什么吧
Girl, you remember something.
他们说了些有关
They said something about
一个叫肖恩・约翰逊的人的事情 肖恩
a guy named Shyne Johnson, Shyne?
肖恩・约翰逊
Shyne Johnson?
我就说听到了你的声音 你个恶毒的婊子
I knew I heard your voice, you evil bitch!
停下 停下
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
噢我的天呐
Oh, my God!
没事了 没事了 没事了
I got her. I got you. I got you.
-过来 过来 -别碰我 德雷
- Come on, come on. - Get off of me, Dre!
-好了 让我看看 -我的天哪
- It's okay, let me see. - Oh, my God.
你特么到底怎么回事
What in the hell is wrong with you?!
-我知道是你推了我 婊子 -什么
- I know you pushed me, bitch! - What?!
别碰我
Get off of me! Ow!
-冷静 -别碰我
- Calm down. - Get off of me!
不 这指控可没道理啊
No, that's a wild accusation to make!
我下楼的时候摔下来昏迷了
I passed out on the way down,
等我醒来的时候 看到了你的鞋
and then I woke up and I saw your shoes.
那双你特别喜欢的
The bottom of those
红色鲁布托高跟鞋
red Louboutins you love so much.
-我的天哪 她疯了 -等等 不 不
- Oh, my God, she's crazy! - Wait, no, no, no.
朗达 很多女人都穿这种鞋啊
Rhonda, a whole lot of women rock them shoes.
我就有一双
I got a pair.
-朗达 -你现在帮她说话了
- Rhonda... - You're on her side now?
我没有帮谁说话 我只是说
I'm on nobody's side, but I'm saying
我没法想象她会做这样的事
I can't see her doing that.
好了 等一下
Okay, wait a minute.
都冷静 朗达
Hold up. So, Rhonda,
你真的认为这个像乡下人进城的的安妮卡
you really think pearl-clutching debutante Anika
会把你推下楼梯
pushed you down the steps?
我知道是你做的
I know you did it.
我怎么可能对你做出那样的事 朗达
How could I do something like that to you, Rhonda?
噢 闭嘴吧 婊子
Oh, shut up, bitch!
告诉他们 德雷
Tell 'em, Dre.
告诉他们
Tell 'em.
德雷
Dre?
我们很抱歉
We're sorry.
哇哦
Wow.
-我们很抱歉 爸 -抱歉
- We are sorry, Pop. - Sorry?
我不知道这是发生了什么
I don't know what's going on here.
我们没想在你的办公室
We didn't mean to come into your office...
很抱歉
We're sorry?
搞出这样的闹剧 这么丑态百出
...like this, with this type of energy.
我们非常抱歉
We're very sorry.
你太可悲了
You are pathetic!
-很抱歉 -她还好吧
- Sorry about that. - Is she okay?
是的 没事
Yeah, it's okay.
我的天哪 她疯了
Oh, my God, she is crazy!
我绝对不会做这样的事情
I could never do something like that!
好了 帮她清理一下 让她冷静下来
Okay, go clean her up. Calm her down.
没事了 没事了
I got you. I got you.
别让她流产
Before she lose the baby.
嘿 还有和她呆在一起 直到我们
Hey, and stay with her till we get her
-给她配好安保 -没问题
- some security. - I'm on it.
她不会被传唤的
She won't be subpoenaed.
既然我没有怀上他的孙子
Now that I'm not carrying his grandchild,
我们就又对他毫无价值了
we are nothing to him again.
然后他会让那婊子逃过这一劫
And he's gonna let her get away with it.
他们不相信你 朗达
They don't believe it, Rhonda.
什么
What?
他们不相信你
They don't believe it.
我也不相信
And neither do I.
什么
What?
那你的幻觉呢
What about your visions, huh?
那是因为我的病 宝贝
It's part of my illness, baby.
你自己也是这么说的
You said so yourself.
好吧 如果现在上帝告诉了你
Well, if God was telling you
有人把我推下楼梯
that somebody pushed me down the stairs,
那我可能就开始信主了
I might have to start actually believing in him.
那你想要我们怎么做
Well, what do you want us to do?
我为了你
What I did for you.
对弗农做的事
With Vernon.
我一点也没犹豫
I didn't hesitate.
那是自我防卫 朗达
It was self-defense, Rhonda.
-我去 -那是自我防范
- Oh, God. - It was self-defense.
得了吧
Come on.
你知道 你的两个兄弟都是音乐家 对吧
You know, your brothers are both musicians, right?
他们这天赋是继承自卢修斯
They got that from Lucious.
但你所继承的
But what you got,
除了他母亲的疾病以外
aside from his mother's illness,
就是他的杀手天性
is his killer instinct.
安德雷先生
Mr. Andre?
谢谢你 胡安妮塔
Thank you, Juanita.
-你这话不是真心的 -噢 我是真心的
- You don't mean that. - Oh, I do.
我绝对是真心的
I definitely mean it.
所以 当你真正变成那个我所嫁的男人
So, when you become the man that I married,
那个愿意去做需要做的事情的男人时
the man who's willing to do what needs to be done...
-嗯 -让他给我打个电话
- Mm. - ...have him give me a call
因为我真的很想他
'cause I really miss him.
好的
Okay.
嗯 是啊 想笑就笑吧
Mm-hmm. Yeah, laugh all you want.
我早跟你说过 塔里克会是个大麻烦
I told your ass Tariq was gonna be a problem.
不 他不会很麻烦
Nah, he ain't the problem.
我们有太多重合的人手
We got too many people in common.
问题是
Problem is...
什么
What?
天
Ugh.
到底是什么 卢修斯
What is it, Lucious?
你知道 在你被关起来之后
You know, after you got locked up,
-我得安排一些暗探 -嗯 是
- I had to put in work on a couple cats. - Mm-hmm. Yeah.
毒贩
Drug dealers.
有三个是想要我们死
The three horsemen who wanted us dead.
我明白
I got it.
是 然后还有第四个人
Yeah, well, there was a fourth horseman.
前三个是为了保护我们的家庭
First three was to protect our family.
但是最后一个 是一份工作
But that last one, that was a job.
那你是在替谁卖命 卢修斯
Who were you working for, Lucious?
你知道我是在为谁卖命
You know who I was working for.
是你让他们听到我的音乐的
You was the one that let them hear my music.
汤米・达弗尼和罗西・珀金斯
Tommy Davoni and Rosey Perkins?
就是他们
Exactly.
他们想要一个新歌手打破销售记录
They were cutting a record with this new artist
然而这个歌手却不是善茬
that turned out to be a real loudmouth.
倒卖黄牛票
Selling wolf tickets,
威胁别的歌手
threatening all the other artists,
所以他们就想要做掉他
and so they wanted him handled.
而肖恩和我被挑中做这份工作
And Shyne and me got the memo.
你知道联邦探员不会轻易放过这件事的 对吧
You do realize the Feds aren't gonna let this go, right?
还有谁知道
Who else knows?
你 我 汤米和罗西
You, me and Tommy and Rosey.
但是他们两个
But the both of them,
都会来哈基姆的婚礼
they coming to Hakeem's wedding, you know.
我们还暂且没事
We still tight.
他们现在也开始洗白了 所以事情败露一样吃不了兜着走
And they're legit now, so they got just as much to lose.
好的 好的 这也是联邦探员围着肖恩调查的原因吧
Right, right. And that's why the Feds are all over Shyne.
是 但是肖恩 他是个愚蠢的恶棍 你知道吧
Yeah, but Shyne... he's a idiot thug, you know.
他可不会告密
He ain't no snitch.
只有死人才能知道我们的过去
Know our past got to stay buried.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
不能让别人知道这些事情
No one can know about this.
# I got broads in Atlanta #
# Twistin' dope, lean, and the Fanta #
# Credit cards and the scammers #
# Hittin' off licks in the bando #
# Black X6, Phantom... #
这是肖恩的地方吧
Is this Shyne's spot?
# Going out like I'm Montana #
# Hundred killers, hundred hammers #
# Black X6, Phantom #
# White X6, Panda... #
就拐个弯帮我买点多兹乐糖
How long's it take to go around the corner
能花多长时间啊
and get some Twizzlers?
我半个小时之前让他出去 他怎么到现在都还没回来
I sent him out 30 minutes ago, and he still ain't back.
要是他一分钟后还不回
If he not here in the next minute,
我就把他也装在箱子里
I'm gonna put his ass in a box, too.
让他给我买的是多兹乐糖
Told him to go get Twizzlers,
不是他妈的圣杯
not the damn Holy Grail!
嘿 肖恩
Hey, Shyne.
最好是我的多兹乐到了
That better be my Twizzlers.
你和琦琦・里昂有约吗 她上楼来了
You expecting Cookie Lyon? She on her way up.
她来晚了
She late.
# Black X6, Phantom #
# White X6, Panda #
# Pocket swole, Danny #
# Selling bar, candy #
# Man, I'm the macho like Randy #
# The choppa go Oscar for Grammy #
# You need to pull up ya panty #
# Hope you killas understand me... #
马力欧
Mario.
让她进来
Let her in.
# Panda. #
听着
Look.
我想说的是 一旦你们其中一个倒下
All I'm saying is if one of y'all goes down,
其他所有人也得倒
all of y'all go down.
所以你们不觉得互相帮助才是明智的吗
So don't you think it'd be smart if y'all had each other's backs?
卢修斯把我踢出局
Lucious cut me out.
他发的唱片欠我一份酬劳
He owe me profits on his record.
肖恩 你自己也清楚
Shyne, you know damn well
那张唱片跟你半毛钱关系没有
you ain't have nothing to do with that record.
好吧 听着
Okay, look.
你想要多少钱
How much is it gonna take to make this right?
我不想要他的钱
I don't want his money.
嗯 那你想要什么呢 肖恩
Well, what do you want, Shyne?
我想帮我的侄子乔伊争取到一份出版协议
I want a publishing deal for my nephew Joey.
这孩子很有天赋
This kid hella talented.
他在这里没机会出人头地
He can't catch a break out here.
嗯 对此我很遗憾
Mm, sorry to hear that.
-对不起 -听听这个
- Sorry... - Check this out.
# It's Hakeem the Dream, I ain't talking about Olajuwon #
# Uh-uh, it's the Empire's El Capo-tin #
# And we don't care who we stepping on #
# He better know who you're betting on #
# Make sure your weapon drawn 'cause we shooting... #
给 肖恩
Here, Shyne.
这不是多兹乐糖
These ain't Twizzlers!
好了
Okay.
成交
Done.
并且我想要哈基姆来录
And I want Hakeem to record it.
没问题
I can make that happen.
而且
And...
我想参加婚礼
I want to come to that wedding.
业内的人都被邀请了 除了我
See, everybody in the industry got invited but me.
我得说
And I got to say...
我很受伤
my feelings are hurt.
回家的感觉很好 对吗
It's good to be home, right?
是啊 当然
Yeah, sure.
我厌倦了当你的护士 兄弟
Yo, I'm tired of being your nurse, bro.
我还有别的事要做 好吗
I got other things to do, okay?
我还有两天就要结婚了
I'm getting married in two days.
好吧 没事 因为首先
All right, that's cool, 'cause first of all,
我不需要你们帮我擦屁股
I don't need y'all to babysit my ass.
你们走吧
So be gone.
-你确定吗 -我确定
- You sure? - I'm certain.
你确定吗 我们可以给你放个电影或者游戏
You sure? We can put a movie on or a game.
我不想看什么游戏
I don't want to watch no damn game.
你们可以退下了 走吧
You're dismissed. Go.
好吧 如果有需要随时打给我
All right, hit me up if you need something.
再见 我爱你们
Bye. I love you.
我也爱你 傻子
Love you, too, fool.
那么 朗达真的走了吗
So, Rhonda really left?
是的 我们有个大学同学
Yeah, we got a friend from college
刚刚 呃 在洛杉矶开了一家珠宝公司
who's, uh, starting up a jewelry company in L.A.
她过去瞧瞧
She went to check it out.
她会回来的
She'll be back.
是啊 是啊 她当然会回来了
Yeah, yeah. Of course she'll be back.
别告诉贾马尔 好吗
And don't tell Jamal, okay?
我不希望再有什么事烦他了
I don't want to give him anything else to brood about.
听着 我很担心他 德雷
Look, I'm worried about him, Dre.
是啊 我也是
Yeah, me, too.
所有人都在努力帮他 你知道吗
And everybody's trying to help him, you know?
我 你 琦琦 贝基
Me, you, Cookie, Becky.
所有人 除了
Everybody except...
卢修斯
Lucious.
拜托 伙计
Come on, man.
卢修斯什么时候
When's the last time
大发慈悲帮过别人了
Lucious went out of his way to help anybody?
尤其是他自己的儿子
Especially one of his own sons.
你们有十分钟
You got ten minutes.
你伤透了我的心你知道吗 弗雷达
You know you broke my heart, Freda.
你为什么要朝我开枪
Why would you try and shoot me?
你知道这是为什么
You know why.
我不知道
I don't know why.
你杀了我父亲
You killed my father.
卡萝尔告诉我的
Carol told me.
你干嘛相信那个瘾君子的话啊
Why would you listen to a crackhead?
听着 我与你父亲最后的谈话
Look, the last conversation I had with your father
是关于你的
was about you.
不然你认为我为什么
Why do you think I tried to reach out
一开始去找了你
to you in the first place?
因为你感到愧疚
'Cause you felt guilty.
你想想我和你父亲一起长大的情谊
The circumstances under which me and your father grew up,
我会伤害他吗
the violence?
正因如此 当我看到你去探望他时
That's why, when I saw you when you came to visit him,
我看到了你身上的天赋
and I saw this talent in you that...
值得被挖掘的天赋
that was something worth saving.
我向你保证
Promise you,
我从未伤害过你爸爸
I never laid a finger on your daddy.
但这件事已经与他无关了
But this ain't about him no more.
这与我儿子有关
This is about my son.
我的儿子贾马尔
This is about Jamal.
你关心他 对吗
You care about him, right?
你知道我关心他
You know I care about him.
是的 嗯 他目前情况很糟糕
Yeah, well, he's in a real bad place right now.
而且不管怎么说
And no matter how you spin it,
他之所以会这样子也是因为你的选择
he's in that place because of the choices that you made.
现在
Now...
我并不在乎其他人是怎么看我的
I don't really care what anybody think about me.
没错 我是个自私的混蛋
Yeah, I'm a selfish son of a bitch.
生活造就了现在的我
Life made me like this.
但是
But...
贾马尔不是混蛋
Jamal's not.
所以我想帮助他
And I'm here to help him.
但是没有你的话我也帮不上忙
And I can't do that without you.
我写了个曲子
I wrote something.
给
Here.
如果重新开始播放
If you can start this over,
我想我有了点想法
I think I got something.
嗯 如果你有什么想法 不如把它录下来吧
Well, if you got something, why don't we just record it?
# I wake up in the morning, what I'm thankful for #
# But you, my God, is what I'm thankful for #
# I can see my life, it flash behind yours #
# But when I look at you, I'm seeing so much more #
# I thank God I could never get enough of this #
# Now I'm hearing they want me, I'm such a lucky bitch #
# I'm no killa, but on me I'm-a clutch the fifth #
# But when I'm with you, boy, we on a different tip #
# A different tip, I'm a survivor #
# You know I been through this, it's like I live through this #
# Everybody know Freda, she hit the ground and go #
# You put me in the booth and we tore it down fo' sho' #
# It was time when I didn't have nothing, you was there for me #
# Instead of pretending, acting just like you cared for me... #
嘿 马尔
Hey, Mal.
我今天去见了弗雷达
I went to see Freda today.
她说什么了
What'd she say?
对着我没说多少
Not much to me.
她 呃 一直很顽固
She was, uh, stubborn till the end.
我说想帮她找代表律师
I offered to help her with her legal representation,
但是她拒绝了
but she refused.
那是因为她很正直 爸爸
It's 'cause she has integrity, Dad.
是啊 嗯 最后她还是接受了
Yeah, well, in the end, she accepted it.
她拜托我给你个东西
She wanted me to give you something.
还有我想说的是
And just so you know,
我今天了结了这个恶性循环
I ended the cycle today.
她不再生气了
She ain't mad no more.
# I wake up in the morning #
# What I'm thankful for #
# But you, my God, is what I'm thankful for #
# I can see my life, it flash behind yours #
# But when I look at you, I'm seeing so much more #
# I thank God I could never get enough of this #
# Now I'm hearing they want me, I'm such a lucky bitch #
# I'm no killa, but on me I'm-a clutch the fifth #
# But when I'm with you, boy, we on a different tip #
# A different tip, I'm a survivor #
# You know I been through this, it's like I live through this #
# Everybody know Freda, she hit the ground and go #
# You put me in the booth and we tore it down fo' sho' #
# It was time when I didn't have nothing, you was there for me #
# Instead of pretending, acting just like you cared for me #
# And you now I never ran, never will, homie... #
# There's been a few times you cried #
# And even more times they lied #
# Messing with the wrong crowd #
# Feeling like a big cloud's... #
# There's been a few times you cried #
# Even more times they lied #
# Messing with the wrong crowd, feeling like a big cloud's... #
# La, la, la #
# Suddenly the guards have changed #
# I'm whispering your name. #
干杯
Toast!
敬新婚夫妇
To the new couple.
敬劳拉和哈基姆
To Laura and Hakeem.
明天 你们两位将在里昂家族的名义下
Tomorrow, you two will be joined together
携手步入婚姻殿堂
in holy matrimony under the Lyon banner
为帝国公司再续辉煌
to carry on the Empire.
-阿门 -干杯
- Amen. - Cheers!
-干杯 -干杯
- Turn up! - Cheers.
玛丽亚告诉我肖恩・约翰逊也要参加婚礼
Maria tells me Shyne Johnson is coming to the wedding.
这是真的吗
Is this true?
肖恩・约翰逊是谁
Who's Shyne Johnson?
嘻哈乐界最臭名昭著的恶棍之一
One of the most notorious thugs in hip-hop.
你听说过他 亲爱的
You've read about him, sweetie.
他在拉斯维加斯
He shot up
创立了那间酒吧
that club in Vegas.
为了打败那个白人说唱歌手
He did time for beating that white rapper.
如果他来
Just someone
参加我女儿的婚礼 我会很不快
I wouldn't feel too comfortable having at my daughter's wedding.
嗯 肖恩是我们家的老朋友了
Well, Shyne's an old family friend.
他不会惹麻烦的
He's not gonna be a problem.
嗯 这对我们而言就是个麻烦
Well, it's a problem for us.
我们真的希望他别出席
We would really rather he didn't attend.
听着 玛丽亚 阿图罗
Look, Maria, Arturo,
他们是我父母请的客人 好吗
they're my parents' people, okay?
我尊敬他们的出身
I respect where they come from.
妈妈 爸爸
Mom and Dad,
我娶劳拉的一个主要原因就是
one of the main reasons I'm marrying Laura
为了摆脱那段历史
is to break away from that history.
就像贾马尔说的
Just like Jamal said.
我们将组建属于自己的家庭 对吗 宝贝
We're gonna start our own family. Right, babe?
我们不用去理会那些破事
And we ain't gonna listen to none of that mess.
你和我将结束那段历史 宝贝
You and me gonna end the cycle, baby.
干杯
Cheers up.
-干杯 -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
干杯
Cheers.
所有人 停下 停下 停下
Y'all, stop, stop, stop!
你们俩都挺好的
You both are good.
TT 你的大提琴声音一点也不突出
T.T., your cello is getting completely lost.
在声乐之间 你得把音量
So in between the vocals, you need to make it soar
再提高一些
a little bit more.
拜托了 这非常关键
Come on, that's a real moment.
这是为我弟弟的婚礼而演奏的
It's for my brother's wedding.
必须要惊艳 惊艳
It's got to soar. Soar!
从第65小节开始重来
Measure 65 again.
嗯 我们的首要任务是
Well, our first priority
为哈基姆和贾马尔准备新的专辑
is getting out new albums for Hakeem and Jamal.
贾马尔
Jamal?
嗯 我跟他简单谈了一下
Well, I had a little talk with him,
我很确信他会写点新歌
and I'm pretty sure some music is gonna come from it.
那么 有什么想法吗
So, any thoughts?
妈 爸 快来 有急事
Mom, Dad, come quick. It's an emergency.
等我们一下
Give us a minute.
她的保镖没来得及阻止
She just ran right out there before her bodyguard
她就跑上去了
could stop her.
噢 天哪
Oh, my God.
安妮卡
Anika!
-安妮卡 -妈
- Anika? - Mom.
安妮卡 怎么回事
Anika! What's going on?
回去
Get back.
安妮卡
Anika?
发生什么了 宝贝
What's going on, baby?
哈
Huh?
我宁愿自杀
I'd rather kill myself
也不想被迫揭发卢修斯
than to be forced to snitch on Lucious.
不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
我们不会让你陷入那种境地的
We're not gonna let that happen to you.
他们会逼我作证 他们会
They're gonna make me testify. They're gonna put me in
把我列入证人保护计划 我做不到
the witness protection program. I can't do that.
告诉她 卢修斯
Tell her, Lucious.
嘿 我有好消息要告诉你
Hey, I got good news for you.
瑟斯发现联邦调查局必须在大陪审团前
Thirsty found out that the Feds got to put on their trial
进行审判
before the grand jury...
在一天半之内 亲爱的
...in a day and a half, sweetheart.
所以你只需再多冷静两天
So all you got to do is be cool for two more days.
安妮卡
Anika?
听着
Look...
我知道我俩之间有过不和
I know we had bad blood between us.
但你肚子里还有个生命
But you are carrying a life.
我的孙子
My grandson.
所以你决不会是孤独一人
So you'll never be alone.
你听到了吗
You hear me?
因为我明白孤独的滋味
'Cause I know what that feels like.
你现在是里昂家族的一员了
You're a Lyon now.
好吗
Okay?
这不就是你一直所求的吗
Isn't that what you always wanted?
哈
Huh?
成为我们中的一员
To be one of us?
对吗
Yeah?
我知道
I know.
会没事的 我知道
It's gonna be okay. I know.
会没事的
It's gonna be all right.
来吧 会没事的
Come on. It's gonna be all right.
来吧
Come on.
嘿 来看看
Hey, check it out.
-我们从转接那里开始吧 哈 -好的
- Let's take it from the bridge, huh? - Okay.
大家准备好了吗
Everybody ready?
二 三
Two, three,
四 一
four, one...
# Whoa-o, whoa-o, whoa #
# Ooh, ooh-ooh #
# Ooh, ooh-ooh... #
你知道吗
You know I came by
我去医院看望过你 但你爸没让我进去
the hospital to visit you, but your dad didn't let me in.
# Ooh, ooh-ooh #
# I'm-a keep on loving #
# Loving you #
# Ooh, ooh... #
大家 大家
Y'all. Y'all.
杰夫 杰夫
Jeff. Jeff.
首先 我很喜欢
First of all, I love it.
-谢谢 伙计 -我真的很喜欢
- Thank you, man. - I really do.
呃 唯一一个我觉得需要改动的地方是
Um, the only change that I would say is
当我在唱这一句的时候 呃
there's a moment where I'm singing, um...
# I'm gonna keep on loving you. #
不要 呃
So instead of, um...
不要只是“噢噢噢Oohs”这样和声
instead of just doing the "Oohs,"
能不能这样唱 呃 “Loving you”
can we just say, uh... # Loving you. #
-噢 好的 我喜欢 -好的
- Oh, yeah, I like that. - Yeah.
大家明白了吗
Everybody got that?
二 三 四 一
Two, three, four, one...
# Whoa-o, whoa-o, whoa #
# Loving you #
# Just keep on loving you #
- # Loving you... # - Ah!
不 不 不用 我没事 我没事 我没事
No, no, no, no, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
你没事吧
You all right?
-你确定吗 -是的 是的 我没事
- You sure? - Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
呃 这样吧
Uh, you know what?
我们待会再继续
Let's just continue this later,
等贾马尔感觉好些了
when Jamal feels a little better...
不 没必要
No. Absolutely not.
别听他的 拜托 大伙儿
Do not listen to him. Come on, y'all.
我们明天之内必须做好
We have to be done by tomorrow.
我没事 继续吧
I'm fine. Come on.
我很好
I'm okay.
-是吗 -我很好
- Yeah? - I'm fine.
你别乱着急
Calm that ass down.
-二 三 四 一 二 -来吧 大家 一起唱
- Two, three, four, one, two... - Come on, y'all, let's sing.
# Loving you #
# Said it feels good #
# Just to keep on loving you #
- # Hey, said it feels good # - # Loving you #
# Just to keep on loving you, oh #
- # Said, oh, baby # - # Loving you #
# Ooh #
# Loving you #
# Loving you... #
你为贾马尔所做的事
What you did for Jamal...
没别的人能办到 卢修斯
nobody else could've done that, Lucious.
拜托
Come on.
搞得我一直在想
Got me over here thinking
也许你根本没那么坏呢
maybe you ain't the devil after all.
怎么 你觉得我关心那个孩子吗
What, you think I care about that boy?
他替我挣了好多好多钱
He make me a whole lot of money.
-啊 -住嘴
- Ah! - Stop it.
你知道我喜欢你下手更重一些
You know I like it when you do it harder.
噢 得了吧
Oh, God.
我发誓 我希望联邦调查局能放过这些破事
I swear, I hope all this crap is over with the Feds.
尤其是他们在大陪审团面前拿不出任何证据
Especially when they come up empty with the grand jury.
嗯
Mm.
是啊 嗯 他们似乎退缩了
Yeah, well, they seem to have backed off.
也许怪人塔里克被钳制住了
Maybe Tariq the Freak got his wrist slapped.
你知道吗 如果你当时在我身边
You know, none of this stuff would've happened
这一切都不会发生
if you'd been around.
没了你我什么也不是
I was never any good without you.
够了 卢修斯
All right, Lucious.
-别说这些话了 伙计 -怎么了
- Stop all that talk, man. - What?
你知道我俩的这个话题从来不会和平收尾的
You know that never ends well for me and you.
别说了
Cut it out.
我不该放你走的
I should've never let you go.
我没再婚是有原因的
There's a reason I never married anybody else.
听着 我们还是先把你儿子明天的婚礼办完再说吧
Look, let's just get your son married tomorrow.
那之后也许我们能聊聊这个
Maybe we'll talk.
噢 我喜欢也许
Ooh, I like maybe.
让我们为也许干杯吧
Let's toast to maybe.
也许
Maybe.
-也许 -也许
- Maybe. - Maybe.
也许你那根软面条还能用
Maybe if that noodle works.
再给我一颗伟哥就行
Give me one of them blue pills.
再见 卢修斯
Good-bye, Lucious.
-肮脏的老男人 -嗯
- Dirty old man. - Mm!
-嗯 -我喜欢看着你走开的样子
- Hmm. - I like watching you walk away.
我知道你喜欢
I know you do.
给我看看
Twerk it for me.
啊 啊 啊
Ah, ah, ah...!
不要盯着我看 啊 啊
Get your ones out. Ah, ah...!
# I can show you something #
# That ain't none of them can #
# 'Cause I, 'cause I #
# 'Cause I ain't too cool to dance... #
真帅
So handsome.
连你也能这么帅 哈基姆
Even you, Hakeem.
我不知道为什么之前觉得你很丑
I don't know why I thought you were ugly.
奶奶
Grandma.
真的吗
Really?
奶奶 你之前说我们 呃
Grandma, what did you mean when you said that we were, um,
是为爸爸的爸爸偿还血债是什么意思
paying for the crimes of Dad's dad?
德怀特不喜欢我提这件事
Dwight don't want me talking about that.
嗯 我们就是我们 奶奶
Well, we are who we are, Grandma,
不管我们父亲是否愿意谈论这个
despite whether our father wants to talk about it.
嗯 你是对的
Well, you're right.
你逃不掉的
You can't escape it.
这存在于他的血液里 还有他的大部分表亲
It's in him, it's in most of his cousins,
还存在于
it's bound to be
你们三个的血液里
in you three.
或者至少你们其中之一
Or at least one of you.
至于乔
As for Joe...
嗯 乔罪有应得
well, Joe got what he deserved.
等等 乔
Wait, Joe?
那是 那是我们的爷爷
That's... that's our grandfather.
你死定了 乔
You're a dead man, Joe.
他亲眼看着他父亲在自己面前死掉吗
He saw his father die in front of him?
谁杀了他
Who shot him?
别信她跟你们说的任何话
Don't believe anything she tell you.
实际上 她只是在说我们看起来都很帅
Actually, she was just telling us how handsome we all look.
对吧 奶奶
Right, Grandma?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
来吧 哈基姆
Come on, Hakeem.
来迎接你的客人们吧 伙计
Let's go welcome your guests, man.
走吧
Let's go.
-为什么一定要做这个 -为什么一定要做这个
- Why we got to do it? - Why we got to do it?
因为这是你的职责
'Cause it's your job!
# You say we fight #
# I'll say we argue #
# Maybe you're right #
# That we really are through... #
哈基姆 我很气你们
Hakeem, I'm mad at y'all.
你们没准备鸡肉 没准备猪排 什么也没有
Y'all ain't got no chicken, no pork chops, no nothing.
嗨
Hi!
我不得不自己带甜甜圈过来
I had to bring my own doughnut.
把这个拿走 波莎 给我一个拥抱
Get that out of here, Porsha. Give me a hug.
# That's what I'm gonna do... #
嗨
Hi.
# You say it's mine... #
罗西 你看起来可不像六十多岁的样子啊
Well, Rosey, you don't look a day over 60.
你知道我还能更年轻点的 琦琦 跟我聊聊
You know I roll younger than that, Cookie. Talk to me.
你最好小心点 别把卢修斯惹毛了
You better watch out. Don't you piss Lucious off.
喔
Ooh.
嘿 主人公到了
Hey, there he is.
新郎官 恭喜啊 哈基姆
Man of the hour. Congratulations, Hakeem.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
你确定要结婚吗 年轻人
Sure you ready to do this, young man?
我结了三次婚
I did it three times,
现在我就得给三份赡养费了
and now I got three alimony checks.
得了吧
Cut it out.
我从未对任何事这么确定过
Look, I never been so sure about anything.
-好的 祝你好运 -好吧
- All right. Good luck to you. - Okay?
罗西
Rosey!
怎么了 我的兄弟
What's up, my brother?
-好的 -汤米 汤米
- All right. - Tommy, Tommy.
-你还好吧 我的朋友 -感谢你们捧场
- How are you, my friend? - Thank you all for coming.
你们都知道我的儿子 贾马尔
Y'all know my son Jamal.
是啊 我密切注意着你的动向呢
Yeah. I been watching your every move.
我很为你在美国之声音乐奖上的表演自豪
I was proud of you at the ASAs.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
是啊 全世界都为他自豪
Yeah, the whole world was proud of him.
我是在说他替你挨枪子儿之前的事 里昂
I'm talking about before he took that bullet for you, L.
我简直等不及看你甩掉你爹妈
I can't wait to hear what you do
之后会做什么事
when you cut loose your father and mother.
-别 -你怎么总想挑起事端呢 伙计
- No. - Why you trying to start stuff, man?
伙计 老鹰注定要翱翔天际
Man, eagle got to fly.
不 不 这一切都是因为爱 你知道吗
No, no, it's all love, you know?
不过我现在正在准备我的新独唱
I am doing my new single though.
是由D总监制作的
And it's, uh, it's produced by D-Major.
很好
All right.
# That's what you want me to #
# Ooh... #
-太棒了 -太棒了
- Yes. - Yes!
无与伦比
Fantastic!
我们最顶尖的歌手之一
One of our number one artists.
噢 那是谁
Oh, what's that?
等等 等等 等一下
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
# Let the champagne spill... #
拿着这个 宝贝
Hold that, baby. Uh.
呃
Mmm!
Mmm! Mmm.
看看那个小丑 你居然邀请了肖恩
Look at that clown. You invited Shyne?
他带着妓女参加你儿子的婚礼
He brought hookers to your son's wedding.
噢 噢 看看他
Oh, oh! Uh! Look at that!
我走了 里昂
I'm out of here, L.
-别 别 不要这样 -不 不
- No, no, no, no, no. Come on. - No, no, no, no.
跟我们到另一个房间去
Come with us into the other room.
联邦探员还在周围四处查探
Feds is still sniffing around,
我们必须确保肖恩举止不出格
and we have to make sure Shyne behaves.
这些主要是为了预防
It's precautionary, mostly.
他们并没有查出些什么
Mad 'cause they got a bag full of nothing,
就是有群傻缺们想要用我并没有
just a lame-ass task force who came up empty
做过的事情嫁祸给我
on something I didn't do.
可怜的卢修斯
Free Lucious.
演出很棒
Hell of a concert.
是的 谢谢
Yes, thank you.
你们肯定都知道联邦探员是怎么工作的
Now, uh, you guys know how the Feds work,
不然你们这些年也不会尽可能远离他们
or else you wouldn't have stayed clear of them all these years.
所以我们让肖恩闭紧大嘴巴
So it is very important that we keep Shyne
是非常重要的
as a part of our circle of silence.
是 但如果有人早就把肖恩供出来了
Yeah, but if somebody already gave them Shyne...
这也就意味着肖恩不是我们唯一的麻烦
It means Shyne's not our only problem.
我们有几个朋友
Well, there was a couple of friends that...
我们这么说吧 他们不会再告密了
Let's just say they're not around to snitch anymore.
他们最近都退休了
They've recently retired.
但是 肖恩不一样
Now, Shyne on the other hand,
你知道 他就是小屁孩
you know, he's just a kid.
他想要再次进入我们的圈子
He wants to be part of the club again.
好吧 卢修斯
All right, Lucious.
但是肖恩不会带来什么好东西的
But nothing good can come from Shyne's punk ass.
了解
Understood.
我们就给他点甜头尝尝 好吧
We'll just entertain him for a bit, okay?
玩好婚礼这场局
Let's go do this wedding.
就这么办
That's a plan.
我们爱你 亲爱的
We love you, my darling.
我们只希望你能得到最好的
We only want the best for you.
我们希望哈基姆能守护你
We hope Hakeem keeps you safe.
我现在跟你们所有人讲
I'm putting you all on notice right now.
我兄弟马上就要推出一张专辑
My brother about to drop this album.
而你们所有人都会想要分一杯羹 这张专辑绝对会火
All y'all gonna want a piece of this one. It's hot.
嘿 我知道这一切都很疯狂
Hey, I know it's all crazy,
但是会有好结果的 好吗
but it's all gonna work out, okay?
谢谢你捧场 安妮卡
Thank you for coming, Anika.
安妮卡・卡尔汗 你被传唤了
Anika Calhoun, you've been served.
-法庭见 -什么
- See you in court. - What?!
-不 -发生了什么
- No! - What's happening?
阻止她
Stop! Stop her!
-滚开 -先生 别挡道
- Move! - Sir, get out of the way!
放手
Get off!
呵 大陪审团
Mm-hmm. Grand jury.
这特么都是发生了什么
What the hell is going on?
什么
What?!
别碰我
Get off me!
这就是我之前担心的
This is exactly what I was talking about.
我不允许你嫁给他了
I'm putting a stop to it.
肖恩 你他妈就是个蠢蛋
Shyne, you're a damn fool!
这就是我们一开始抛弃你
That's why we dumped you the first time
让你呆在你应该在的地方的原因
and why we keep your ghetto ass in place!
劳拉 等等
Laura, wait!
宝贝 一切都在我掌控之中
Baby, I got it all under control.
就是有点小争执
It was just a little argument.
没事的
It's gonna be okay.
不可能没事 哈基姆
It's not okay anymore, Hakeem.
我不能
I can't.
我不要过这样的生活
This isn't gonna be my life.
-我很抱歉 -宝贝 我很抱歉
- I'm sorry. - Baby, I'm sorry.
我不能嫁给你
I can't do this.
放手
Let go of me!
一切都会没事的
It's gonna be all right.
你们就是一群恶棍
You're all a bunch of thugs.
拜托 不要走
Please don't go.
好了
Okay.
所有人都给我滚蛋
Everybody get the hell out of here.
滚
Go on!
就现在
Now!
我说了滚
I said go!
-快滚 滚 -卢修斯 别这样
- Walk away. Go! - Lucious, stop it!
我不是说着玩的
I'm not playing!
韦伯 关上门
Webb, shut the door!
好了 听着 告诉我该怎么做
All right, look, just tell me what to do.
只要不出庭作证 我做什么都可以
I'll do whatever it takes in order to not testify.
好 不管了
Okay, the hell with it.
瑟斯
Thirsty,
-如果安妮卡和我结婚了 -等下 怎么回事
- if Anika and I get married... - Wait, what?
-联邦探员就不能强迫她出庭作证了 对不对
...the Feds can't force her to testify... right or wrong?
-卢修斯 -我也想到过这个办法
- Lucious. - That thought crossed my mind,
但是你需要一张结婚证
but you'd need a marriage license.
联邦探员肯定会阻止你的
The Feds would definitely block that.
我们在华盛顿特区订婚的时候
We already got that covered
就已经拿到证了
when we were engaged in D.C.
卢修斯 我警告你
Lucious! I'm warning you.
你警告我什么
You're warning me what?
不行 你不能这么做 这是我的婚礼
No, you can't do it. This is my wedding.
她怀着我的孩子
She carrying my baby.
是啊 伙计 我们脑子都坏了吗
Yeah, man, are we sick or something?
我们本应该终结这个循环
Is... We were supposed to end the cycle.
当准备好的时候 循环就会自动终止
Cycle ends when it's ready to end.
而在那之前 我们要做必须做的事情
Till then, we do what we have to do.
我救这婊子的命 不是为了让她毁了我的
I did not save this bitch's life so that she could ruin mine.
肯定还有别的办法
There's got to be another way.
不 没有别的办法了
No, there ain't no other way.
听着 听着 这一切都是表面用来哄人的
Look, look, this is just a paper game.
都不是真的 对我们俩的关系不会有任何影响
It ain't real. It doesn't affect where you and I are.
嘿 卢修斯 必须要今晚完成
Hey, Lucious, this has to be done tonight.
我们要么同生 要么共死
We're ride or die.
我需要你和我站在一起
I need you on this one.
你要和我站在一起渡过这个危机
You got to ride with me on this one.
你们都知道我爱你们 对吧
Y'all know I love you, right?
你们都知道
You know.
我也会为了挽救我的家庭
And I'm-a do whatever I can...
做任何事
to save my family.
但是我和你们父亲
But me and your daddy...
我做不到
I can't do this.
别碰我
Get your hands off me!
妈
Ma.
不 不
No. No.
安妮卡・卡尔汗 你是否愿意接受
Anika Calhoun, do you take Lucious Lyon
卢修斯・里昂作为你合法丈夫
to be your lawfully wedded husband?
我愿意
I do.
卢修斯・里昂
Lucious Lyon,
你是否愿意接受安妮卡・卡尔汗作为你的妻子
do you take Anika Calhoun to be your wife?
我愿意
I do.
凭借我被纽约州
With the powers conferred on me
所赋予的权力 在上帝和你们的
by the state of New York, before God...
家人面前
...and your family,
我宣布你们结为夫妻
I declare you're married.
你可以轻吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
唱歌
Sing.
你听到你爸说的话了 起来唱歌
You heard your father. Get up and sing.
我知道是你推了她
I know you pushed her.
我得离开一会 请原谅
Excuse me for a minute, please.
你完全没想过这孩子
So it just never occurred to you that this kid is gonna be...
你同时会是这孩子的父亲和爷爷吗
you're gonna be his daddy and granddaddy.
事实是怎样就是怎样
It is what it is.
注意点 塔里克・卡泽斯来了
Yo, heads up. It's Tariq Cousins.
别来无恙啊 兄弟
Ooh. What's up, brother?
-什么 -塔里克是谁
- Huh? - Who's Tariq?
恭喜你结成了渎神的婚姻
Congratulate you on your unholy matrimony.
-阿门 -嗯
- Amen. - Mm.
为什么你们什么都
Why y'all keep chasing
找不到 却还是要不停缠着我呢 伙计
after me, man, when you keep coming up empty?
为什么要这样浪费纳税人的钱
Why-why waste the taxpayers' money like that?
这意味着我们资金充足
Means we're well funded.
相信我 我们这才刚刚开始
Believe me, we just getting started.
德怀特 你同父异母的兄弟来这干什么呢
Dwight, what's your half brother doing here?
杀我啊
Kill me.
你就会背上
You'll go down
杀害警察的罪名
for killing a cop.
而你的儿子就会失去他的父亲
And your son will grow up without a father.
那男孩可不是我的儿子 乔
That boy ain't my son, Joe.
他是你的儿子
He's yours.
现在他和德怀特都将失去父亲
Now him and Dwight will both grow up without a father.
爸爸
Daddy!
爸爸 爸爸
Daddy! Dad, Dad, Dad!
爸爸
Dad!
Daddy!
爸爸
Dad...
噢 你是真的不知道啊
Oh, you really didn't know, huh?
是啊 我们的父亲是个好警察 德怀特
Yeah, our father was a good cop, Dwight.
但不是个好人
But a bad man.
我猜我们俩各自继承了他的一半 伙计
I guess we each got half of him, man.
我的名字是卢修斯
My name Lucious.
还有 宝贝 我没有家人
And, baby, I ain't got no family.
嘿 德雷 把我老婆找过来
Hey, Dre, get my wife.
我来
I got it.
你想要这个恶魔的孩子
You wanted that devil child
成为帝国产业的唯一继承人 是不是
to be the only heir to the throne, didn't you?
是不是
Didn't you?!
你说的太多了 是我做的 婊子
You're damn right I did, you bitch!
不
No!